<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-12-09T22:46:34-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Kinky Femdom Stories</title><subtitle>Best Sexy Femdom Stories</subtitle><entry><title type="html">My first play</title><link href="/stories/first-play/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My first play" /><published>2019-04-08T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-04-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/stories/first-play</id><content type="html" xml:base="/stories/first-play/">&lt;p&gt;Hello, and let’s start…
At some point i started to really like female domination (femdom) porn,
and somehow got those roleplay fantasies in my head about oral servitude,
it just appeared very hot to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That would be my very first roleplay fetish experience, being dominated by arrangement, 
this story is real as it gets.
One of the evening i posted my ad with description of my roleplay fantasy on one of the escort fetish websites.
The description was fairly short and straight forward about me looking to play a submissive role in ass, pussy licking scenario and that i need a bossy woman that will use me well…
A couple hour later i got a response from some woman, she sounded fairly nice, but intriguing, normally there is a lot of spam, but this one seemed real…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She asked if i would be interested in serving her the way i described, alogn with providing a donation, and i asked her for some details, since donation is involved and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said that she was actually in this lifestyle and not only doing this for donation, but because she likes doing it and has a lot of experience and passion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to double check if we understood each other right, because i knew that there is a lot of “Pro Dommes” that are actually  doing only “clothed” sessions (which means they remain dressed and only may facesit you or verbally dominate), which i was not interested in, and she sent me back some very sexy GIFs with fully naked women riding guys faces and she added:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“That it was a level of the game I am looking for”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I gotta say it got me very excited and horny, i was hard withing a few seconds an of course aggreed to book a session, the i asked for her photo, she sent me one, very plain, nothing exciting, but also good looking photo i guess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We aggreed on a date and time, then she said she will host it at her appartment and discretion is a must, which was not a problem at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she told me she will confirm the session the day before arranged date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She sent me another email a day before arranged session with the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Hi my servant, read my instructions carefully and do not dare to not follow them,
you will arrive in time and not later, if you are early, then sit somewhere outside and wait till the time comes.
The moment you enter my bedroom, you will kneel, and be prepared to use your mouth for whatever i tell you!”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This got me really excited again, i aggreed on this terms and got ready for the next day session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I arrived earlier and was very excited. i never really had a sub/dom session like this before.
Finally it was the time, so i rang the bell and she buzzed me in the building, i got up on the second floor and saw her standing in the door inviting me in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She looked quite attractive, maybe a bit chubby, sot of cute face, wearing only inderwear and leather white/green/red corset top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I walked in and handed her the donation, there was a guy sitting in a leaving room, turned out to be her husband, which did not bother, because we headed to her nedroom and that man never interfered or said anything. 
Once we stepped in the bedroom, she closed the door and said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Kneel”,
so i did…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she looked at me and said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Look at you, sub, with your weird fantasies, what a naughty boy”,
her tone was kind of bossy and even a bit mean.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She told me to take all my cloth off and get back on my knees,
after that she handcuffs on my arms with some sort of noise chains, she said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“I’m gonna hear it every time you are trying to play with yourself, so you can’t, unless i told you so, Understood?!”
I said: “Yes Mistress, understood”.
Then she left the bedroom for a minute and told me to think about what kind of naughty pathetic sub i am…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When she came back, she sat on a bed right in front of me and told me that she expects a lot from me today, and withing the next 2 hours i will have to deliver her quite a few orgasms the way she wants it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She ordered me to start licking one of her feet, and made me suck in her toes.
I was not reallyinto feet that much, so that was not really exciting, but obviously she liked it, so i could not refuse and did what she said, besides my dick was hard as hell anyay, i was very excited already.
Then she told me to do the same with her other foor, and i did that for a few minutes…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that she walked around the bedroom for a few seconds and started taking off her panties, saying:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“This will be on the way…”,
then she got on the bed again, got on her knees and hands on the bed, like a doggy style pose, turned her ass im my direction moved a bit closer to me and her ass to my face and said:&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“You are gonna lick my ass now”, and by that she meant her asshole, she added:&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Get you mounth here, find my ass and lick it!”, she said that in a very bossy tone, so i would not dare to refuse…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So i did get my face very close to her kind of large ass, my face was so close, i could even slightly feel the smeel of her horny pussy, then i got my tongue out and pushed it right into the crack, from bottom to top, on the way i briefly felt her asshole with my tongue, i could not see her asshole, because her butt chick were not spread, byt i could feel it once i ran into her hole with my tongue.
I could also feel a lot of pussy juice taste on the lover side of her crack and asshole also had a bit different taste, not a bad taste byt maybe some sort of unscented lube or something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she yelled:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;” Come on, eat my ass, stick your tongue right in there!!!”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was a bit hesitating, since i never ate ass before and never had this kind of roleplay, so i lust licked the surface of her ass for like 30 sec, slightly putting the pressure with my tongue, so she could feel me licking her asshole.
Finally i got courage to stick my tongue into her ass, as deep as i could, she ordered:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Yes, fuck it with your tongue!”, and i was doing it for a few minutes, until she stopped me…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she turned on her back and opened her legs wide, i could see her soaking, big pussy lips, her pussy was verry wet and slightly hairy, i could feel her smell a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“You know what’s next”, she said.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Get your mouth over here and suck my lips clean!”, she told me, and by that she meant her big wet cunt lips, she pressed my head right in there, and i started doing what she told me to. I could feel salty taste of her juices, i can’t say i was enjoying iy, but i also had no choice, she was sort of forcing my mouth right in her soaking cunt…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So i lickid her pussy lips clean and started on the deeper part, she ordered me to stick my tongue inside her pussy as deep as i could and fuck her with my tongue till she will orgasm. My god, that cunt was large and very wet, felt like half of my face were fitting in there and was being wrapped by those pussy lips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was gong on for a bit, maybe 20-30 mins, i could feel her cumming a few times, then she finally stopped me, she walked over to her dresser, pulled out a condom and handed it to me, she said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Put it on!”
So i did, and after that she climed back on the bed and turned her ass to me, she said:&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Go for it, fuck me from behind”, i did not hesitate and climed on the bed, and stuck my 9 inch hard dick in her soaking pussy, it slipped in easely, she was so fucking wet, i strated fucking her rather aggressively, and within maybe a minute, she was screaming that she’s cumming…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, she pushed me away immideately and said that i’m done, i can’t come fucking her, that was only to get her orgasm, and now i have to get back on the floor on my knees and stick my face in her crack, so my nove would be in ger asshole and my mouth would be eating her cunt that i just fucked and clean it, she also said that while i’m doing it, this is my only chance to jerk off and have an orgasm and i got only 60 seconds, after that we are done…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So i rushed on the floor and stuck my face in her soaking of her own cum crack, started licking her cunt off and jerking myself off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She started giving me directions again, she said if her cunt is not clean withing a minute of her cum and juices, she will punish me and piss in my mouth and make me dring it, so i really tried my best to not be forced to drink piss…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was cumming very strong after 40-45 seconds and luckly cleaned her pussy good, so she said that i did ok, and i’m free now, i must get dressed and leave quickly, i got dressed and left her apartment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was my first fetish experience, i hope somebody enjoyed my story.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello, and let’s start… At some point i started to really like female domination (femdom) porn, and somehow got those roleplay fantasies in my head about oral servitude, it just appeared very hot to me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Black Hottie</title><link href="/stories/black-hottie/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Black Hottie" /><published>2019-04-08T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-04-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/stories/black-hottie</id><content type="html" xml:base="/stories/black-hottie/">&lt;p&gt;Hello, here is my second story…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some time passed after &lt;a href=&quot;/stories/first-play&quot;&gt;my first fetish play experience&lt;/a&gt; and i started looking online for another adventure, with the forced oral servitude scenario.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A while later, some lady responded to my ad, she sent a few very straight forward images with her asshole, which kind got me horny and i invited her to meet at my place the same day, later. I was very excited and asked to play quite dominant, and not take  a “no” for an answer, you know what i mean… She agreed with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I met her by my building and talked to her for a minute, she seemed nice and very attractive, she was wearing sexy boots on a medium height hill and tight jeans, pretty face as well. She was a bit chubby, but not more than i’d like, so that was making her even hotter, nice size bubble ass all tied up in a jeans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked her once again if she was ok with playing the way i asked and would use me good, she said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Don’t worry, i will!”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we went inside the apartment and one i closed the door, she told me to go down on my knees and move closer to my bed.
After that she took of her jacket and purse, started taking off her tops and told me to take off my shirt as well, i did that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When she took off her bra, i noticed very large gorgeous tities, they looked great, not saggy or anything.
She said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Come over here and sink your face right between them”, i did that, that was so hot, they were worm and soft and smelled very good, like some nice porfume…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that she pushed me away a bit and told me in a very bossy tone:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“You can call me mistress, and only do what i ask and when i ask! I’m very horny now, and i will use you to deal with it, don’t even think about using your dick or even toching it, until i cum at least once. I will come very strong and cum will come out of my pussy, i may even squirt a bit, so be ready to take it all in your mouth and swallow, understand?!”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I said: - “Yes Mistress, i understand”, even though it sounded kinds weird and scary, even gross…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She took off her jeans, her legs looked sexy, then she took off her panties and shove it in my face, told me to sniff it…
I had not choice but to do it, it actually smelled like porfume, was very good smell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she turned around and leaned a bit forward, moving her large tight ass closer to my face, she open her but cheeks a bit and i could see her dark asshole and part of her pussy, which was wet, she was not kidding about being horny, i could see a lot of white stuff surrounding her pussy lips…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Stick your face in my ass and sniff if, i want to feel your nose right on my asshole!”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I kinda got lost for a second, and was about to say no or making some kind of excuse, but before i said anything, she slightly slapped my face and yelled:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Do i dave to repeat myself?! Sniff my fucking asshole!”, and she slightly pusshed my head towords her ass.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had no choice and got my face right in her crack, started making sniffing noise, it actually smelled nice, like porfume, but i could also feel her horny smell, coming from pussy, it was so wet, i could feel it was wet…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She rubbed her asshole on my nose for a bit, maybe 10-15 seconds, like she wanted to fuck it.
Then she stopped and went on a bed and got in a doggy style pose, her ass was facing my face, she still had those sexy hill boots on, it looked so hot…
She slightly opened her legs and her big hot butt cheecks opened a bit too, i could her her black cunt cover in white juice all around and her ass crack was open, she said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“I really wanna orgasm, you are so going to lick my ass and i will rub my cunt”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She turned around for a second and told me to take of my pants, she said she want to see if my dick is hard, and of course it was hard, then she told me to get closer and open my mouth, i did that and shit gently spit in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that she turned her large ass back to my face and told me to stick my tongue right in her crack astart licking her ass, just to lick it first with the flat tongue, she wants to feel me licking her back hole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got my face very close to her butt and could see her asshole and dripping pussy, i think she was just teasing herself, because she was ready to cum, she needed like one touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I put my face between her cheecks and started licking ass, she moaned right away, pretty loud, i thing i got a part of her pussy with my tongue by accident, i got a lot of her horny salty cream on my tongue, she slapped my face a bit and said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Don’t touch pussy till i say so, only lick shithole right now!”
She was not touching her pussy either, but i know she wanted to, maybe was just tesing herself more and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few miutes later, she told me to stop for a second and stick out my tongue as far as i can, when i did that, she told me to stick it all the way in her ass and start moving it back ind forth all the way, she said i have to fuck her tight hole very good with my tongue…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried to push it in all the way, her ass was very tight, i took a few strokes to push it deeper, and she moaned again, a lot and loud, her ass tasted fine, it was clean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I kept sticking my tongue deep as i could, she yelled “deeper!” and slapped me a bit again, i tried but my tongue is not a dick, although i really wish at that moment that i could stick my dick in her ass, my dick is quite long, like 9 inch, would probably hurt her a lot…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, she stopped me for a second, she told me to lie on the bed, face up, and she said she is gonna sit on my face, fucking my tongue with her ass and rub her pussy now, as she will say that she is cumming, I will have to move my mouth a bit up and open it wide and wrap it around her pussy and be ready for a surprise and she will keep rubbing clit and cumming hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got a bit worriad about the “surprise” she reffered to, but i did not have a chance to ask really, she landed her crotch right on my face, she set facing me, moved a few forword so my tongue would stick right down her back hole, and her legs were wide open, all the horny cunt juice was licking on my face, i saw her pussy wide open, she had a nice smelling little bush above her clit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She started moving on my tongue up and dow and rubbing her socking pussy, mostly clit, then after 20 - 30 seconds she started moaning and moving a bit more agressively, then she yelled:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Cumming! Open your mouth!”,
I opened my mouth wide and she moved a bit lower, almost all her vagina was in my mouth, i was licking it a bit and it was so slimy ane salty and slippery and wet….
A few seconds later she started shaking and yelling that she’s cumming again, felt like all her vagina was moving by itself a bit, then like 5 secons later something dripped in my mouth, some liquid that felt like gelly a bit or something, hard to tell, and a few seconds later quite a large amount of salty liquid shot out right in my mouth, i freaked out a bit and tried to move my head to the right to spit it out, but she did not let me do it, she held my head still and slightly slapped my face and told me to swallow it, since i had no choice, i managed to swallow that squirt…&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Good boy!” she said,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Stick your tongue back to my pussy and lick it all clean, my pussy lips”, i did all that, i licked it very clean,then she moved a bit forward and said - “My ass too, all the squirt drops”, i had to lick ass too, it was all kind of sweaty and salty, but it was kind of hot and i could not say no to that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she got up, turned around and pushed her ass a bit backwards, towards me, the she told me to get up on my knees and lick her all her crotch again, so it’s really clean…
I did that, for about 30 seconds, then she told me to stick my tongue deep in ger asshole and move it back and forth, and i did… The taste was much more bitter than before, and all i could think of is to be done with it and finally be able to jerk myself off, and have a nice orgasm…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“That’s enough”, she said, - “You have done alright…”, then she started getting dressed.
I really wanted to cum too and asked her if she would stay for a minute so i could jerk off and cum, but she said that she does not care for what i want and does not want to see me  touching myself and that i can jerk off after she leaves… I was kind of hoping to cum during licking her or at least looking at her ass or pussy or her naked anyhow… so that was a bit dissapointing…&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“However”, she said, - “I need to pee and fix my makeup, so you can lick me clean after i take a piss if you want, and you can jerk off while doing that”, i agreed to that, since i had no other choice.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She went to the bathroom and i walked in with her, she pulled down her pants and panties and sat on the toilet, she told me to get down on my knees right in front of her and watch her piss. She opened her legs a bit wider and i could see her pissing.
When she finished, she moved a bit closer, to the edge of the toilet and told me tolick it clean. I started moving my face closer and was about to pull out my cock to jerk of, but she stopped me and said: - “Not yet, i don’t want to see you touching yourself”, i got a bit confused, but started licking her pissof her crotch, a few drops of it were running down to her asshole still. She got up and turner around, she took a step closer to the mirror and started looking for something in her purse, she told me that she will be fixing her make up now, while i will have to finish up licking her cleanand now when i’m behind her, i can quietly jerk off too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So i pulled my dick out and started licking her ass, u cluld not reach  pussy much from that position, but i did not care, i was about to explode, i really enjoy jerking myself at that moment while licking her shithole, i shot a huge load almost immediately in my hand to not get her pants dirty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Well”, she said. - “I’m done here” she pulled her pants back up.
I walked her to the door, stepped outside with her for a second, she told me to open my mouth and crotch down a little,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Here is a kiss”, she said, and spit in my mouth. Then she said bye and walked away…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello, here is my second story…</summary></entry></feed>